execunet.com 2019-12-18

# ExecuNet | ExecuNet

_Updated May 25, 2018_

All personal information given to ExecuNet is kept in strictest confidence.

Personal information you provide us is used solely by ExecuNet and is never sold or given to third parties for any purpose without your approval. We collect this information merely to enable us to better serve your needs, to inform you about updates to ExecuNet services, and to alert you to products and services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We are strongly committed to protecting your privacy online and have taken steps to protect the information you share with us. For example, we use SSL encryption technology to safeguard your credit card data when used in electronic commerce transactions. To help us protect your privacy, you should maintain the secrecy of username and password you may have set up in connection with your participation in any ExecuNet service.

**ExecuNet’s Privacy Commitment**

ExecuNet is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We want to provide a safe, secure user experience. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private and is used only for the purposes as set forth herein.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This Privacy Policy covers ExecuNet’s treatment of personally identifiable information that ExecuNet collects when you are on the ExecuNet site, and when you use ExecuNet’s services. This policy also covers ExecuNet’s treatment of any personally identifiable information that ExecuNet’s business partners share with ExecuNet.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that ExecuNet does not own or control, or to people that ExecuNet does not employ or manage.

**Using ExecuNet Connections**

ExecuNet encourages members to contact other members to enhance and expand their network, to refer or recommend a resource or service, and to pass along information that is deemed beneficial. We ask that you please adhere to the following guidelines:

  * Broadband solicitation to the ExecuNet membership for sale of products or services that result in personal gain or are for the enrichment of the company they work for is not allowed. Example: Dissemination of an e-mail to the membership to gain clients for legal advice, financial services, multi-level marketing firms, etc.
  * Broadband solicitation to the ExecuNet membership to express a personal, religious or political point of view, or to elicit member opinions is not allowed. Example: fund raising requests, flyers of any type, surveys and questionnaires.
  * Examples of allowed solicitations to the membership: job postings, asking for company information, asking for information on an individual, recent announcement on new government policy on extending unemployment benefits, etc. (Contacts are limited to 100 members per week.)
  * ExecuNet has established a Referral Center on the Members Only website where our members may communicate to the membership benefits that may be of value to the membership even though such benefits may also result in personal gain. Examples currently on the website: career coaches, resume writers, conference calling services, guide to self-employment, etc.

ExecuNet reserves the right to monitor and terminate any contact and/or solicitation it considers compromising to its membership or its position. Please report inappropriate communications to our Member Services Team at [member.services@execunet.com](mailto:member.services@execunet.com). Should Member Services receive five or more complaints regarding inappropriate communications from a member, ExecuNet reserves the right to terminate access to Networking privileges.

**Information Collection**

When you register as a member of ExecuNet, we ask for several kinds of personal information, such as: your name, e-mail address, zip code, career level, occupation, industry, and functional interests. ExecuNet also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your Internet Protocol (IP) address, ExecuNet cookie information, and the page you requested. ExecuNet uses this information for four general purposes: to customize the content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to inform you about updates to ExecuNet services, and to alert you to products and services that we believe may be of interest to you.

**Information About All ExecuNet Visitors**

In general, we gather information about all of our users collectively, such as what areas users visit most frequently and what services users access the most. We only use such data anonymously and in the aggregate. This information helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall experience for you. We may share this information with our partners, but only in the aggregate, so that they too may understand how ExecuNet visitors use our site.

**Information About You Specifically**

In some instances, when you sign up to use a service, respond to an offer, or purchase a product, for example, we may need more specific information about you, such as name, address, phone number, e-mail address, credit card number, etc. During your visit to ExecuNet, we may also ask you for other information, such as information on your interests, your likes and dislikes regarding the site, the types of negotiations and career information you are interested in, etc., in an effort to deliver to you the best possible site experience.

These types of personal information are used solely by ExecuNet and are never sold or given to third parties for any purpose without your explicit approval.

ExecuNet also provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of various types of communications. If you choose to receive these types of communications at the time of registration, but later decide you no longer want to receive them, simply communicate your preferences to our Member Services Team either via phone or e-mail.

**General Information Disclosure**

Except as described in this privacy policy, we do not disclose information about your individual visits to ExecuNet, or personal information that you provide, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, personal references, etc., to any outside parties, except when we believe it is required by law or to protect ExecuNet, our users or others. But, we may record and share aggregated information with our partners.

Also, if you input your information on a co-branded registration page, such as that of an ExecuNet and partner company-sponsored service or product, then your information becomes the property of both ExecuNet and the partner co-sponsoring the product or service, as that partner may collect such personal information from you once you leave ExecuNet’s site. In that instance, the use of your personal information by our partner company will be subject to the privacy policy of that company, and ExecuNet is not responsible for their use of your personal information.

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include hosting our web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing other services. These other companies will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any third party.

**Updating Account Information**

ExecuNet allows you to change or correct your personal information at any time. To do so, simply call our Member Services Team at 800-637-3126 and you will be able to update the information you have submitted.

**Online Order Security**

When you place an order online, your personal details and credit card information are scrambled using SSL encryption technology before being sent over the Internet. Although we cannot guarantee encryption or the privacy of your personal details and credit card information, SSL makes it very difficult for your information to be stolen or intercepted while being transferred.

Our credit card transactions are processed by Merchant e-Solutions (https://www.merchante-solutions.com/). All information sent to Merchant e-Solutions is in the secure SSL environment, which will protect it against disclosure to third parties. When we receive your order, it is on an SSL server. For further information about Merchant e-Solutions’ privacy statement, please [click here](https://www.merchante-solutions.com/privacy-policy/).

**Cookies**

To enhance your experience at ExecuNet, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a “cookie.” Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to enable our systems to recognize your browser, remember your preferences, track visits to understand visitor usage and behavior, and plan for increased loads. Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster service, consistent, updated results, and a more personalized site experience. Our goal is to make your experience with ExecuNet more convenient and personal. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies. However, doing this will hinder performance and could negatively impact your experience on our site. We use tools and applications to evaluate usage of our Site. We use these tools to help us improve our services, performance and user experiences. We do not share your personal information with these third parties. However, these third parties may combine the information that we provide about you with other information that they have collected. This Privacy Policy does not cover such third parties’ use of the data.

**Feedback**

ExecuNet has an area on the site where you can submit feedback. Any feedback that is submitted through this area becomes the property of ExecuNet. We may use this feedback, such as success stories, for marketing purposes, or to contact you for further feedback on the site.

**Privacy Commitment Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy commitment for ExecuNet, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about ExecuNet’s privacy commitment, please feel free to e-mail us at [member.services@execunet.com](mailto:member.services@execunet.com) or call **800-637-3126** and speak to one of our representatives.

ExecuNet uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security.

This privacy policy is not intended to, and does not, create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
